{
    "id": "170d7b9cfdf942feabf7a7d7613a442d",
    "title": "Would Or Should",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "The postman …………………. be here soon.",
            "description": "We use should to indicate possibility.",
            "answers": [
                "should",
                "would"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "62975ecac5d54a44875602fbd8723750"
        },
        {
            "question": "…………………………. we invite Mark?",
            "description": "We use should to ask for a suggestion.",
            "answers": [
                "Should",
                "Would"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "9ab84be6a8fb4717895d1165c4b6aa2a"
        },
        {
            "question": "She ………………………… be told.",
            "description": "We use should to express necessity.",
            "answers": [
                "should",
                "would"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "2cf4b2377c28443986f37cd8e17e6f15"
        },
        {
            "question": "People …………………….. drive more carefully.",
            "description": "We use should to express necessity.",
            "answers": [
                "would",
                "should"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "31e724a45eb74affb742a3df5033ec3d"
        },
        {
            "question": "You …………………………… do things like that.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "wouldn't",
                "shouldn't"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "e6661dd94eb74149801acc2f2f6c1330"
        },
        {
            "question": "I …………………………. come tomorrow if I got time.",
            "description": "In the second conditional, we use a past tense in the if-clause and would + infinitive in the main clause.",
            "answers": [
                "would",
                "should"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "63345337667a4f9aba5e9a6a264578f7"
        },
        {
            "question": "I ………………………………. be grateful for an early reply.",
            "description": "Both would and should can be used with the first person pronouns with little difference of meaning.",
            "answers": [
                "would",
                "should",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "df920d8c393849faa25de80a89010a9d"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………………. you like some help?",
            "description": "We use would in polite offers and requests.",
            "answers": [
                "Would",
                "Should",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "79e79c8688494a1cbfcd471b88ef0471"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………………. I go and see the police?",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Should",
                "Would",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "3539925cc3bd455284072a22b86191d8"
        },
        {
            "question": "I knew that I ………………………… talk to her, but it seemed too difficult.",
            "description": "Should indicates necessity or obligation. ",
            "answers": [
                "would",
                "should",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "bdbe7071092a4a01a11072f3de18b777"
        },
        {
            "question": "I …………………………. have sent the money this morning, but I forgot.",
            "description": "Should have is often used to talk about past events that did not happen. ",
            "answers": [
                "should",
                "would"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "3795fbc07f3f4f7d943e2576d8054f92"
        },
        {
            "question": "You ……………………………. have shouted at her – it really upset her.",
            "description": "Should not have is often used to talk about unwanted things that happened. ",
            "answers": [
                "should not",
                "would not",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "5d93f3361ead42409b3b234a451fb059"
        }
    ]
}